necklace3 =[
  {"question":"衣裳","Answer":"yīshang"},
  {"question":"顯得","Answer":"xiǎnde"},
  {"question":"美艷動人","Answer":"měiyàn dòngrén"},
  {"question":"出席","Answer":"chūxí"},
  {"question":"宴會","Answer":"yànhuì"},
  {"question":"長官","Answer":"zhǎngguān"},
  {"question":"興奮","Answer":"xīngfèn"},
  {"question":"滿場","Answer":"mǎnchǎng"},
  {"question":"蝴蝶","Answer":"húdié"},
  {"question":"一輩子","Answer":"yībèizi"},
  {"question":"宴會","Answer":"yànhuì"},
  {"question":"披","Answer":"pī"},
  {"question":"粗陋","Answer":"cūlòu"},
  {"question":"深夜","Answer":"shēnyè"},
  {"question":"寒風刺骨","Answer":"hánfēngcìgǔ"},
  {"question":"哆嗦","Answer":"duōsuo"},
  {"question":"召","Answer":"zhào"},
  {"question":"瑪蒂達","Answer":"mǎdì dá"},
  {"question":"模樣","Answer":"múyàng"},
  {"question":"突然","Answer":"tūrán"},
  {"question":"脖子","Answer":"bózi"},
  {"question":"項鏈","Answer":"xiàngliàn"},
  {"question":"嚇呆","Answer":"xiàdāi"},
  {"question":"瑪蒂達","Answer":"mǎdì dá"},
  {"question":"陣","Answer":"zhèn"},
  {"question":"暈眩","Answer":"yūnxuàn"},
  {"question":"蹤跡","Answer":"zōngjì"},
  {"question":"宴會","Answer":"yànhuì"},
  {"question":"丈夫 沿","Answer":"zhàngfu   yán"},
  {"question":"摸過","Answer":"mōguò"},
  {"question":"一無所獲","Answer":"yīwúsuǒhuò"},
  {"question":"報社","Answer":"bàoshè"},
  {"question":"登廣告","Answer":"dēngguǎnggào"},
  {"question":"警察局","Answer":"jǐngchájú"},
  {"question":"報案","Answer":"bàoàn"},
  {"question":"瑪蒂達","Answer":"mǎdì dá"},
  {"question":"心神不定","Answer":"xīnshénbùdìng"},
  {"question":"呆","Answer":"dāi"},
  {"question":"傍晚","Answer":"bàngwǎn"},
  {"question":"一念沮喪","Answer":"yī niàn jǔsàng"},
  {"question":"扣","Answer":"kòu"},
  {"question":"依照","Answer":"yīzhào"},
  {"question":"吩咐","Answer":"fēnfù"},
  {"question":"項鏈","Answer":"xiàngliàn"},
  {"question":"下落","Answer":"xiàluò"},
  {"question":"渺茫","Answer":"miǎománg"},
  {"question":"擔心","Answer":"dānxīn"},
  {"question":"神情","Answer":"shénqíng"},
  {"question":"張","Answer":"zhāng"},
  {"question":"席","Answer":"xí"} 

]